# **Daniel Zhang**



comet2772@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/daniel-zhang-654917219

### Summary

Hello, I'm a professional full-stack developer with years of extensive experience in MERN Stack development. During that time, I have been acknowledged as a solution-focused professional with the ability to design and develop innovative applications using advanced technologies.

I collaborated closely with the application team to develop and implement many full-stack web applications, ensuring optimal functionality, quality and reliability.

#### My skills are:

- Frontend: React, Redux, Angular, Vue, Vuex, Vuetify, Material-UI, JavaScript/TypeScript, HTML, CSS, SCSS, Bootstrap, Gatsby, NextJS
- CMS: WordPress, Shpify, Prismic, Sanity CMS, Contentful
- Backend: Node, Express, RESTful API, Python, Django
- Database: MySQL, MongoDB, PostgreSQL, SQLite
- Cloud Service: AWS, DigitalOcean, Netlify, Heroku, GCP
- Version Control: Git, GitLab, BitBucket, Jira, Trello

I am a goal-driven individual with a strong work ethic who strives to ensure customer satisfaction.

I've spent over 15 years in retail, where I've led teams of 40 to meet the demands of customers purchasing various products through our stores and websites.

I continued to grow my skills with Amazon and took on problem-solving roles, coaching my associates to elevate themselves and learning new processes and technologies.

Thank you

# **Experience**

### Turing Senior Software Engineer

Turing.com

Oct 2020 - Present (11 months +)

# Senior Full-Stack Developer

Upwork

Jun 2016 - Dec 2020 (4 years 7 months)

#### Full-stack Developer

Freelancer

Jun 2015 - Aug 2017 (2 years 3 months)

#### • Frontend Developer

Calibro Corp.

Jul 2013 - Jun 2015 (2 years)

# **Education**



# National Taiwan University

Bachelor's degree, Computer Science Apr 2008 - Apr 2012

## **Skills**

React.js • JavaScript • Node.js • Customer Satisfaction • Web Applications • Good Clinical Practice (GCP) • Bootstrap • Python (Programming Language) • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • MongoDB